[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[PEPPA AND GEORGE SLURPING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are drinking orange juice.
[SLURPING]
[SNORTS]
What noisy little piggies!
[BOTH LAUGH]
George, look at all
the tiny bubbles.
[GRUNTS]
[GIGGLES]
I can make
bigger bubbles.
[INHALES]
[BUBBLES GURGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is blowing bubbles
in her drink.
Hee-hee-hee!
Bub-ble!
NARRATOR:
George wants
to blow bubbles too.
[INHALES]
[BUBBLES GURGLE]
[LAUGHS]
[GURGLING CONTINUES]
Peppa, George, you really
shouldn't play with your food.
Sorry, Daddy.
[GRUNTS]
Peppa, if you
like bubbles,
why don't you play with
your bubble mixture?
Yes! My bubble mixture!
[GRUNTS]
George!
Let's blow bubbles
in the garden.
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is showing George
how to blow bubbles.
First, dip the stick
in the mixture.
[♪♪♪]
Then, take a big breath...
and blow.
[INHALES, BLOWS]
[LAUGHS]
Bub-ble!
[POP]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
George, now it's your turn.
[GRUNTS]
Dip the stick
in the mixture.
Hold it up.
Take a big breath...
[INHALES]
...and blow.
[BLOWING]
NARRATOR:
George is trying really hard,
but he is running out
of breath.
[POP]
Achoo!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
George, you didn't blow
hard enough.
[♪♪♪]
I know a way George
can make bubbles.
Dip the stick
in the mixture...
then lift it up
and wave it around.
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
Bub-ble!
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
It's even better
if you run along.
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS]
Wait for me.
NARRATOR:
George is having fun
making bubbles...
[SNORTING]
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
and Peppa is having fun
popping them.
I love bubbles.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLES]
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear, the bubble mixture
is all used up.
[CRYING]
Daddy, Mommy!
[GRUNTS]
There's no more
bubble mixture.
Don't worry, Peppa,
I have an idea.
[SNORTS]
Mommy Pig!
Bring me
a bucket please.
Yes, Daddy Pig.
Peppa.
Bring me some soap.
Yes, Daddy Pig.
George, bring me
my old tennis racquet.
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
A bucket? Some soap?
A tennis racquet?
What is Daddy Pig doing?
First,
I need some water.
[SPIGOT SQUEAKS]
Then the soap.
[GIGGLING]
And now,
the tennis racquet, please.
[SNORTS]
Thank you.
Now watch this.
[INHALES, BLOWS]
[BUBBLE SNAPS]
ALL: Ooh! Wow!
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig has made
his own bubble mixture.
Come on, everyone.
[LAUGHING]
Be careful, Daddy Pig,
don't slip and fall.
[SNORTS]
I'll be fine.
Whoa! Oof!
Ah! Oof!
Are you okay,
Daddy Pig?
Yes, I'm fine.
Achoo!
ALL:
Wow!
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig has made
the biggest bubble ever.
[POPPING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Oh dear, I've spilt
all my bubble mixture.
Now we can't make
any more bubbles.
Hm.
[SNORTS]
But we can play
jumping in
muddy puddles. Look!
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig's bubble mixture
has made a big, muddy puddle.
ALL:
Hooray!
[SLOSHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
Look! The bubble mixture
has made the puddle all bubbly.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves
jumping up and down
in muddy, bubbly puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up and
down in muddy, bubbly puddles.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends
are going to playgroup today.
The children each have
their own hook
to hang their coats on.
[ALL CONTINUE LAUGHING]
Today we have a new pupil,
Emily Elephant.
KIDS:
Hello, Emily!
Hello.
NARRATOR:
Emily is a bit shy.
MADAME GAZELLE:
Who would like to show Emily
where to hang her coat?
ALL:
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Ho, ho,
we just need one.
Peppa, can you show Emily
where to hang her coat?
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
[GRUNTS]
We each have
our own coat hooks.
This one is for
you, Emily.
NARRATOR:
Emily is hanging her coat
on her very own coat hook.
Now Emily, what would
you like to do today?
Painting, clay
or building blocks?
Um... I don't know.
Maybe building blocks.
MADAME GAZELLE:
And everyone else, painting,
clay or building blocks?
ALL:
Building blocks!
[ALL LAUGHING]
My goodness!
Building blocks
are popular today!
NARRATOR:
Everyone wants to sit
next to Emily Elephant.
[SNORTS]
Emily,
you put one block
on top of another.
Like this.
Woof! Woof! It's better if
you put them side by side.
Baaa!
No, this way, Emily.
Meow! This is
the right way, Emily.
Neigh! No, Emily!
Like this.
You're all being
very helpful.
But Emily, how would you play
with the blocks?
Um... I'm not very sure.
I might do it like this.
ALL:
Wow!
NARRATOR:
Emily Elephant is good
at building blocks.
[RINGING]
NARRATOR:
It is playtime.
ALL:
Hooray! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Emily, would you like to play
outside with the others?
Yes, please.
Can someone show Emily
where we play?
[KIDS LAUGH]
[GRUNTS]
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
[KIDS LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
At playtime,
Peppa and her friends
play in the school garden.
DANNY:
Woof! Woof!
Can't catch me!
[ALL SHOUTING]
NARRATOR: What a lot of noise!
Let's see who is
the loudest.
Okay. I'll go first.
[INHALES]
Squeak! Squeak!
NARRATOR:
That was quite loud.
Now it is Zoë Zebra's turn.
[INHALES, SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
Now Suzy Sheep.
Baa-baa!
NARRATOR:
Now Danny Dog.
Woof! Woof!
NARRATOR:
That was very loud.
My turn! Meow!
My turn! Neigh!
My turn!
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is the loudest.
[KIDS LAUGH]
Emily, you try!
I'm not too sure.
ALL:
Please, Emily!
Okay. I'll try.
[INHALES]
[TRUMPETS]
NARRATOR:
My goodness! That was loud.
KIDS:
Wow!
[GRUNTS]
Do it again!
[INHALES]
[TRUMPETS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Emily is not shy anymore.
[GRUNTS]
Emily,
would you like to play
my favorite game?
What is
your favorite game?
Jumping in muddy puddles!
That's my favorite game
too!
[SLOSHING, LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
Emily loves jumping up and down
This looks like fun.
Yippee!
NARRATOR:
Madame Gazelle loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Everyone loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
[LAUGHING]
Emily, have you enjoyed your
first day at our playgroup?
Yes, Madame Gazelle!
And I see you've made
lots of new friends.
Yes!
Ha-ha-ha!
Emily Elephant
is my friend.
Baa-baa.
And Emily's my friend.
And mine.
[GRUNTS]
Emily,
who do you
like best?
Um... I like Suzy
and Danny and Zoë
and Rebecca and Pedro
and Peppa.
[ALL LAUGH]
[LAUGHS]
[TRUMPETS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Granny and Grandpa Pig
are going on holiday.
They are bringing Polly Parrot
to Peppa's house,
so Peppa and George
can look after her.
[SQUAWKS]
[HORN HONKING, BRAKES SCREECH]
[SNORTS]
Hello, everyone!
Hello, Grandpa Pig!
Hello, Granny Pig!
[GRUNTS]
[SNORTS]
Polly is very excited
about her holiday
with Peppa and George.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Polly.
[SQUAWKS]
[ALL LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Polly Parrot copies
everything that is said.
[SNORTS]
What's in Polly's suitcase,
Granny?
[SNORTS]
This is Polly's food.
George, can you guess
what Polly likes to eat best?
Chocolate
Cake!
[CHUCKLES]
No, not chocolate cake.
Polly likes birdseed.
[SQUAWKS]
Birdseed!
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
Can I feed her,
Granny Pig?
Can I feed her?
[SNORTS]
Yes!
It's very important not to
give Polly too much food.
Yes, Grandpa Pig.
[SNORTS]
Grandpa, can Polly
come out of the cage?
Yes, but you must keep all
the doors and windows closed,
so Polly
doesn't fly away.
Yes,
Grandpa Pig.
[SNORTS]
Goodbye, Peppa.
Goodbye, George.
[SNORTS]
Goodbye, Granny Pig!
Goodbye,
Grandpa Pig!
[SQUAWKS]
Goodbye, Granny Pig!
Goodbye, Grandpa Pig!
[ALL LAUGH]
Would you like
a cup of tea?
[SQUAWKS]
Would you like
a cup of tea?
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
George has got
Polly's birdseed.
[GIGGLING]
PEPPA: George!
That is
too much birdseed.
Polly will grow very big
and burst like a balloon.
Pop!
[SQUAWKS]
Burst like a balloon.
Pop!
[ALL LAUGHING]
[ICE CREAM TRUCK TUNE PLAYS]
[SNORTS]
What's that noise?
Ice cream!
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHING]
[SQUAWKS]
[GRUNTS]
Ice cream, hooray!
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR: Oh dear,
George has forgotten
to close the door.
[SQUAWKS]
[♪♪♪]
Ice cream. Ice cream!
[BELL RINGS]
NARRATOR:
It is Miss Rabbit,
the ice cream lady.
Hello, Mommy Pig.
[GRUNTS]
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
Four ice creams,
please.
Thank you,
Miss Rabbit.
[SLURPING, GIGGLING]
George!
You forgot to close the door!
[SNORTS]
Polly will have flown away!
[GRUNTS]
Don't worry, Peppa.
I'm sure Polly
is still inside.
Polly's not here!
Oh.
[CRIES]
We've lost Polly.
Grandpa and Granny
are going to be very sad.
[SNORTS]
Maybe we should try
the garden.
Look! What's that?
NARRATOR:
What has Mommy Pig seen
in the garden?
[SQUAWKS]
PEPPA: It's Polly!
ALL: Hooray!
[SQUAWKS]
But Daddy, how are we going to
get Polly down from the tree?
[SQUAWKS]
[SNORTING]
Don't worry Peppa,
I'll rescue Polly.
[♪♪♪]
Come on, Polly.
[SQUAWKS]
Would you like
a cup of tea?
NARRATOR:
Oh, no, Polly has flown
higher up the tree!
Oh, dear.
[SNORTS]
Be careful, Daddy!
Don't fall out of the tree
like you always do.
Don't worry, Peppa,
I'll be very careful.
[SNORTS]
Come on, Polly.
[SQUAWKS]
Birdseed!
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
I wonder where
George is going?
George has got
Polly's birdseed.
Polly loves to eat birdseed.
[SQUAWKS]
[LAUGHS]
George has got Polly
down from the tree!
ALL: Hooray!
[ALL SNORT]
[PHONE RINGING]
What's that noise?
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig's mobile phone
is ringing!
What? Whoa! Oof!
[PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
[PHONE BEEPS]
Hello?
Oh, Granny Pig.
Hello, Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
Please, may I talk
to Polly?
Yes, of course.
GRANNY PIG:
Hello, Polly. Are you having
a nice holiday?
[SQUAWKS]
Hello, Polly.
POLLY:
Are you having
a nice holiday?
[BOTH LAUGHING, SNORTING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are going out for the day.
Daddy Pig has made a picnic.
[GRUNTS]
Peppa? George?
Have you got
your stuff ready?
[GRUNTS]
Yes! I'm taking
Teddy.
Dine-Saw!
If you take your toys,
you must look after them.
Yes, Mommy.
[GRUNTS]
[KIDS LAUGHING]
Are we all ready?
[IN UNISON]
Yes, Daddy Pig!
Then let's go!
[STARTS ENGINE]
Dine-Saw!
[CRYING]
NARRATOR:
George has left
Mr. Dinosaur behind.
[CONTINUES CRYING]
Oh, George.
You should take more
care of Mr. Dinosaur.
Dine-Saw!
Are we all absolutely sure we
haven't forgotten anything else?
Yes, Daddy Pig!
[STARTS ENGINE]
Teddy! I've left Teddy!
[BRAKES SCREECH]
Where did you leave Teddy?
I think,
on the kitchen table.
Peppa! You really must
take more care of Teddy.
Teddy! Hee-hee!
[SNORTS]
Here we go again.
[STARTS ENGINE]
All Ready?
[IN UNISON]
Yes, Daddy Pig!
Here we go!
[HONKS HORN]
NARRATOR:
This is the picnic area.
We're here.
Hooray!
[KIDS GIGGLE]
Ahh! I love this picnic spot.
[GRUNTS]
It's so quiet and peaceful.
[MUSICAL CAR HORN PLAYS]
NARRATOR:
It is Zoë Zebra, with her
daddy, Mr. Zebra the Postman.
Hello, Mr. Zebra.
[GRUNTS]
Have you got our post?
Ho, ho.
No deliveries today.
It's my day off.
[SNORTS]
Neigh! We're having
a picnic lunch.
[GRUNTS]
So are we!
I know! Why don't we make
one big picnic?
Yes!
[ALL MUNCHING]
NARRATOR:
What a splendid picnic!
[ALL SLURPING]
[GRUNTS]
Please may George and I
leave the table,
and play with Zoë?
Yes, Peppa.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
[GRUNTS]
Zoe, I've got my Teddy.
I've got my Monkey.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Dine-Saw!
Grrrrrrrrr!
[LAUGHS]
I've got a toy picnic set.
Let's play picnics.
[QUACKING]
Oh, it's the ducks.
They always turn up
when we have a picnic.
We've got pretend
orange juice.
And we've got
pretend cake.
[KIDS LAUGH]
[QUACKING]
It's pretend cake.
It's very nice.
[DUCK QUACKS]
NARRATOR: Oh, dear.
I do not think
the ducks want pretend cake.
Oh, well. That means
there's more for Monkey,
Mr. Dinosaur and Teddy.
PEPPA [IMITATING TEDDY]:
Mm. Delicious!
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Monkey says,
“The best cake ever!"
[ALL LAUGH]
MOMMY PIG:
Peppa, George! Home time!
Bye bye, Zoë!
Bye bye!
Are we all ready?
Yes, Daddy Pig!
[HONKS HORN]
Home time for us
too, Zoë.
Yes, Daddy.
Cups, plates,
Monkey, Teddy...
Oh, no! You shouldn't
be here, Teddy!
NARRATOR:
Peppa has forgotten her Teddy.
Again!
[HORN HONKS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family are home.
Ahh! That's enough driving
for one day.
All I want to do now
is relax,
put my feet up
and watch some--
Teddy!
I forgot Teddy!
Oh, Peppa! Now Daddy Pig
will have to drive
all the way back
to the picnic spot.
Uh... Yes, of course.
[MUSICAL CAR HORN PLAYS]
It's Mr. Zebra, the Postman!
I thought it was your
day off today, Mr. Zebra.
It is my day off.
But Zoë's got
a very special delivery
for a Miss Peppa Pig.
Here you are, Peppa.
What is it?
It's Teddy!
You left Teddy behind,
so we brought him home.
Thank you, Zoë!
Teddy certainly has had
an exciting day out.
But Peppa, you really must
take better care of him.
Yes, Mommy. You are
a very naughty Teddy.
You must promise
not to wander off ever again.
[IMITATING TEDDY]
Sorry, Peppa. I promise.
[ALL LAUGHING,
GRUNTING, SNORTING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[GIGGLING, SNORTING]
KIDS:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING, GRUNTING]
[GIGGLING]
KIDS:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[GRUNTS]